Confucius, Buddha, Jesus...
they all brought light to darkness.
But none of them had one
million subscribers, so...
They... can...
suck it!
Your videos changed my life!
Changed my life!
You are my qu-qu-queen!
_
No, Italian girl.
We are changing the world,
for we are the G-Hive.
And today we are celebrating
our 1 millionth subscriber.
Over 1 million people
are living their lives
according to the Gina-mandments.
They're like the Ten Commandments,
only there's more and they're better.
I would now like to express my gratitude
the best way I know how... through song.
♪ Gratitude ♪
Grati-tat-tat-tat tatitude!
Grati-tat-tat-tat-tatitude!
Gratitude.
Sync & corrections by emeline-whovian
www.addic7ed.com
Guys? Guess who I just
got off the phone with.
My cousin Pam.
What? No. Why would you think that?
You always seemed kind of
jealous of my relationship
with him, so I thought maybe
you called him up to
settle your differences.
I'm definitely not jealous of Pam.
He owns a bird shop.
I barely remember him.
You remember the bird shop.
It wasn't Pam.
No, I was actually talking to
none other than Gina Linetti.
Really?
No one's heard from her in months.
Well, she just invited us
to go check out her new place.
I'm surprised you're
so excited to see her.
I mean, she's been blowing
you off ever since she left.
- What? In what way?
- She bailed
- on your birthday drinks.
- It wasn't that fun.
She was a no-show
at your Secret Santa party!
Christmas is overrated.
- She hasn't called you in months!
- I'm not that interesting.
Look, what is going on with you?
- Are you hangry?
- No. I just ate six hardboiled eggs.
Well, maybe you should've
made it a cool "doz."
Look, I know Gina hasn't
been around very much,
but we're gonna spend
time with her today,
and it's gonna be just like old times.
Gina's gonna be a few minutes.
Her photo shoot is running over.
Yes, Moses! Lookin' good!
Now work those Commandments!
See, Sarge? Just like old times.
Ah, Boyle, there you are.
I have a question for you.
Daddy, wait up!
Oh, your non-adult is
at our place of work
Nikolaj had a half-day at school
for Mariano Rivera's birthday.
I'm watching him on my lunch break.
Nikolaj, say "hi" to Captain Holt.
Hi, Captain Holt! How's Mr. Kevin?
Stressed. His annual budget review
is today, and a recent change
in federal policy
means his grant situation is... tenuous.
- At best.
- Okay.
Hey Nikolaj, Daddy
and Captain Holt need to talk.
Why don't you go do some drawing?
Oh, he loves doing art.
He made a portrait
of our dog Biscuit that had
all of his surgical scars.
Yes. Children are wonders.
I'm conducting a statistical
analysis to get a more nuanced
understanding of which areas
in our jurisdiction
need greater police presence with a hope
of developing a formula that...
What on Walden Pond is this?
Nikolaj, no, that's important!
I'm so sorry, sir. I don't spank him,
but I will reprimand him in my own way.
Niko. I love you.
- I'm so sorry, Daddy!
- No, no, no.
He didn't ruin it, he solved it.
The absolute value of psi.
Nikolaj cracked the equation. Boyle...
your boy is a genius!
Jacob! Terrencio!
Give Moses a hug!
Uhh! It's so good to see you!
Ugh, that shoot took forever.
Did Janelle offer you a snack?
She did. I had Linguini.
So what's been going on with you?
Well, that's actually why I called.
It's not a big deal at all,
but someone's threatening to murder me.
- What?
- Damn, Gina!
I mean, I'm not worried
about it in the slightest.
Anyone who has an online presence
gets meaningless threats.
It actually is a sign that I made it.
- Congrats?
- Thanks, thank you.
The only thing is, I have my
first speaking engagement tomorrow
and the organizer says
he's going to cancel it
unless I have police protection, so...
would you guys come tomorrow
and police protect me?
- Yes, of course, yes.
- Oh, thanks so much.
This is my agent. I'm so sorry.
Duncan, this better be good news.
Oh, it is... your video's
huge, from Spokane to Spain,
you're global, Gines!
Now, let's. Talk. Strategy.
This is gonna take a while.
Do you guys want to get drinks
at Shaw's later and catch up?
Oh, yeah. That sounds really fun.
Great. I'll see you then!
- Okay.
- So, Duncs,
I have an idea for a second book.
It's a memoir, and it's made of memes.
So, it's called a meme-oir.
Whoa, Rosa! What happened?
I touched poison oak.
The doctor says I have to keep
my hands bandaged for a week
so I don't scratch them.
- How did it happen?
- I was on a nature hike
and I went off-trail
to pick a pretty little flower.
Awwww.
Shut up. Now scram.
I have a case report to type up.
Uh, there's no way
you're using a keyboard
with your hands like that.
Oh, I could help you!
Not to brag, but at typing
camp, everyone called me
"The Finger Queen."
Oh, my God, that sounds really dirty.
I swear that's what it meant.
Yeah, it was typing camp.
Nobody thinks that.
Anyway, I don't need your help.
You're really gonna try to make it
through an entire day on your own?
Well, well, well.
Rosa Diaz is finally
gonna learn the lesson
that no matter how strong
she is on her own,
true strength comes from
accepting help from others
That's not what's happening.
Mm-hmm, yeah.
That's how normal people
take their coats off.
I'm fine.
- I can see that.
- This is going well.
Clearly.
Why are you sliding into
my side of the booth?
Because that side is the solo side.
You always put the person
you want catch up with
on the solo side, otherwise
one of us will spend
the whole night straining
our necks looking sideways.
I'm straining my neck
talking to you right now.
Okay, so don't look at me, Terry.
Just face forward. You see me every day.
- Fine.
I gotta say, I'm surprised Gina
invited us to drinks tonight.
She obviously invited us over to her
place because she needed a favor.
Why are you still so down on her?
I've been through this before.
In college, I had a football
buddy, Bryant Ungerbert...
Oh, lemme guess.
You guys were best friends,
then he got drafted into the NFL,
- and now you never talk.
- No, he got drafted into
the Canadian football league,
became a long snapper for Ottawa,
and even that level of
success ruined our friendship.
He's still playing?
How is that possible?
You're 35 to 60 years old.
It's Canada. They don't tackle as hard.
Anyway, his career became
the only thing that mattered.
He was off doing
photo shoots, commercials,
speaking at long snapping conventions...
- Is that a thing?
- In Canada,
it's like the Oscars. Look, the point is
he stopped making time for his friends.
Fine, but that's not
what's happening here.
Nothing has changed with Gina.
- She's not an Ungerbert.
- Hi.
So, Gina won't be able
to make it tonight.
She doesn't have time.
But here are your credentials
for tomorrow's event.
Have a great night.
Oh, no.
She is an Ungerbert.
Hey, Gina's prepping inside.
You get some rest last night?
Yeah, because I got home
from our 9:30 drinks at 9:41.
I was in bed by 10:00.
Then I looked at my phone
for another two hours,
so actually I didn't sleep very well.
But I did realize something.
The only thing that
matters to Gina is work.
You don't say?
Where have I heard that before?
I don't know, Terry. I don't have
time for your weird memory lapse.
I said it last night.
Well, I wish you would've said it to me.
Anyway, I decided I'm not
gonna let it go this time
After we update her on the case,
- I'm gonna say something to her.
- Good.
I wish I'd have said
something to Ungerbert.
Long snapper used to be
my favorite position.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Hmm. Well...
you a weirdo.
Timothée Chalamet,
shimmy-yah, shimmy-yay.
- Gina.
- Oh, sorry.
- I'm doing my vocal warm-up.
- Great.
Well, cyber looked into the threats,
and they traced
a number of negative comments
back to another internet
celebrity, Marvin Lennox.
Marvin Lennox. Yeah,
I'm not worried about him.
- He's an inspirational baker.
- Inspirational baker?
What the hell is that?
A man is like a quiche,
and a quiche is only
as strong as its crust.
What's your crust?
Oh, that's exactly what it sounds like.
Yeah, he's not a threat.
He lives in Utah, and again,
just to remind you...
inspirational baker.
Right. Well, even so,
we have metal detectors
at all of the entrances,
and we'll keep our eyes peeled
for anything suspicious.
Also, before we head in there,
I wanted to talk to you about something.
- What's up?
- Well, it just kind of
bummed me out that last night
you blew us off.
For work. Again.
What? Uh, no.
I did not miss drinks for work.
I had food poisoning.
Did Janelle not tell you?
- No.
- Wow, that's crazy.
'Cause I specifically told her
to tell you... you know what?
- I'm gonna fire her.
- You don't have to do that.
- Janelle.
- Oh, God, doing it now?
- Hi, Gina.
- Okay.
Well, Sarge and I
should probably hit it,
get back in there, survey some people.
But have a great show.
Janelle, just remember
you're gonna have a lot of jobs
in your life... this is but
a blip on your résumé.
Okay Sarge, let's go.
Wanted to see me, sir?
Yes, I wanted to talk
to you about Nikolaj.
How long have you known he was a genius?
I mean, I always knew he was bright.
I just never realized he was that smart
Well, there's no sugarcoating it.
- You're a terrible father.
- What?!
You've been asleep at the wheel, man!
What have you done to cultivate
his incredible mind?
- I read to him every night.
- Shakespeare? Tolstoy?
- No, nothing that advanced.
- Egads, are you reading him Dickens?
- Yes?
- Boyle!
My father never saw my potential.
In grade school, I wanted
to spend all my free time
drawing graphs and charts, but
he insisted I play basketball.
As if I care about
slam dunking a three-pointer.
Don't be my father, Boyle!
I wouldn't dare!
What do you think I should do?
Let me tutor Nikolaj.
Nothing too strenuous.
Maybe some geometry,
statistical mechanics,
perhaps some Latin lyric
poetry thrown in for fun.
Oh, I don't know. He's really booked.
I guess I could cancel
his cartooning class,
- but he really loves it.
- Don't do that.
I hate to think of
all the great cartoons
humanity missed out on because Einstein
was just too busy reinventing physics.
Okay, I'll cancel the class.
I mean, who needs relativity when
we could've had Einstein's take
on lasagna-eating cats.
- I said I'd cancel.
- Did he hate Mondays?
We'll never know.
Okay, I'm going, I'm going!
Ugh, why won't this
dumb monitor turn on?
Because you can't work
without your hands.
Trust us. If you could do this job
without lifting a finger,
we would've already cracked it.
Because we're lazy boys.
I'm just not doing it hard enough.
- Mmm!
- Ooh!
That's a double-sponger.
All right.
I am cleaning this up,
and no one is helping me.
Not a problem.
Because we're lazy boys.
You gotta be kidding me!
_
In the beginning, there was nothing.
And then God, a woman, said,
"Let there be Gina!"
Gina! Please look at me!
You're welcome.
Aaaaah!
It's gonna be hard to spot
a crazy person in here.
- They're all crazy.
- Tell me about it.
This is more insane than the crowd
at the Carly Rae Jepsen
I mean Slayer concert.
G-Hive!
Are you ready for
three new Gina-mandments?
Number one.
You can be anything
you set your mind to...
as long as you're already great at it!
Number two.
No one knows you can't take it with you!
Be buried with your money.
Cha-ching!
Number three.
If you fall down nine times...
you gotta reassess your walking,
'cause something's wrong.
And now, I wanna hear
from you, my baby G-Hive!
Yes, girl in the mustard sweater.
Hi, Gina. I just quit my job
and left my husband who loves
parkour more than he loves me.
And it's all because
of your Gina-mendment:
"If the light in your house
is dim, change the bulb."
Yes!
I have time for 15 more compliments.
Hey, Jake. I think Lennox is here.
I see him. You get him.
I'll stick with Gina.
Uh-oh. He's moving.
Coming through.
There's too many hoodies. I lost him.
- Get Gina out of here, now!
- And now the time has come
for y’all to meditate.
Close your eyes while I sing to you.
♪ Breathe in, breathe out ♪
♪ I invented meditation ♪
- R...
- Gina, we gotta go.
- Lennox is here.
- Told you I'm not worried about Lennox.
Well, it's not your call.
- We're leaving.
- Jake, you're overreacting.
On second thought, maybe we
should get out of here.
- Okay. Kitchen's all clear.
- Bedroom's clear.
Can't believe I just escaped death!
I haven't felt this alive since
I almost got killed by that bus.
I know, right? What a rush.
Feel just like Kevin Costner
in "The Bodyguard"!
What? If anyone's
like Kevin Costner it's me.
I'm the one carrying Gina!
Well, I think we can agree
we were both Kevin Costner.
- No!
- Jake, that was so dope
when you were like, "Clear a path!"
Guys, uniformed officers
found Marvin hiding in
a bathroom at the event space.
He's in custody. We got him!
That's great!
I hope they give him the chair.
Ooh, we should celebrate.
Champagne's in the fridge.
On it.
Duncan, I almost died. It was amazing.
I heard all about it, Gines.
Look, you're trending!
And from my pain comes triumph!
Love that. And we can use this publicity
to get more money out of
those bottled water guys.
You really impressed them
at drinks last night!
Uh, yeah, yeah, yeah... we
should talk about this later.
Sorry, you're breaking up.
Look, I said they loved you
at the drinks last night...
the drinks last night
that you had with the water people?
Crap, I just hit
the Holland Tunnel, but again,
great job with the drinks last night!
Bye.
Jake, did you hear that?
I did, and there's
been a change of plans.
I'm gonna take a rain
check on the champagne,
but it was wonderful seeing you.
Why are you talking
like a flight attendant?
This is how I always talk
when everything is okay.
Which it is right now.
Please enjoy the rest of your day.
How did Nikolaj do?
Were you able to overcome
- my horrible parenting?
- No, it's far worse
than I could've ever imagined.
I showed him a periodic
table, and he thought
it was a coloring book illustration.
I blame myself.
It's such a classic Boyle trait
not to recognize talent.
My cousin Susan didn't know she
could sing until her late 40s.
Honestly, given the hole
that you've put him in,
he needs more expert
help than I can provide.
But, there is...
a boarding school
in Switzerland that would be
a perfect fit for him.
He can enroll immediately.
In Switzerland? I'd never see him.
Then uproot your life
and move there with him.
No one here would miss you.
Hmm. We could live in Gruyere,
the fondue capital of the world.
Oh, I don't know.
It's such a big change.
Well, he's the genius.
Why don't we ask him
what he wants to do?
Good point.
Niko? We need to talk.
Wait. Why is he writing the solution
to my formula for no reason?
And why is he drawing
colorful underpants beneath it?
Oh, I see what's happening.
He's drawing Boy Riga,
loyal sidekick to his favorite
cool superhero, Captain Latvia.
That's his symbol.
He distributes grain evenly
among the working class.
Uh-huh. I see.
So this was all just some coincidence.
He wasn't writing absolute value of psi.
He was just...
doodling.
Aaaah!
Raaah! Uhhh! Ahhh!
Rosa? Are you stuck in there?
No, I'm in here by choice.
Oh, 'cause I hear some banging noises
as if someone was struggling
to open the door.
No. That was the pipes.
Or, is it the sound of you
learning how to ask for help?
You know, you can't spell
"independent" without "dependent."
And you can't spell "Go [bleep]
yourself" without "[bleep] you.
Jake, I had a work thing.
I can't believe you're being
such a baby about this.
I'm not being a baby.
Look, I'm sorry I lied, okay?
It was a big opportunity for me.
I was having drinks
with the brand director
of a bottled water company.
I can't say which one, but it
rhymes with, "fart water."
Perhaps one day I will laugh at that.
In the meantime, I'm happy
for all your success.
I hope your partnership with
"fart water" is very fruitful.
- Good day.
- Come on, dude.
- Just talk to me.
- I would if we were friends,
but you're making it it very clear
that we are not, so I shan't.
- Oh, you're shanting me?
- Yeah, that's right.
- Jake!
- Can't hear you.
- You're shanted!
- Jake!
I told you I only talk to my friends.
No, Jake.
I think I just got stabbed by that guy.
Oh, yeah, ya did.
Ya definitely did.
Okay. The ambulance is on its way.
They said not to remove the knife.
Great.
What's up? I got your text...
Oh, my God, Gina,
there's a knife in you!
Jake, did you stab Gina?
I didn't stab Gina, okay?
Lennox wasn't our guy.
The real perp did it.
He's in a black hoodie and jeans.
He ran that way.
- I'm on it.
- I want you to stay calm
and just try to keep all of your blood
- inside your body.
- Bitch, what do you think I'm doing?
Yeah, I don't know why I said that.
Bring your ass down here so
we can finish our conversation.
We can do that later, Gina.
First of all, I have
so much adrenaline pumping
through my body right now
I can feel almost nothing.
Secondly, you can't say no to me.
- I have a knife in my back.
- Yeah, that tracks.
Okay, fine. So I was saying that
ever since you left you've
been kind of a crappy friend.
Brrrrrawwwwwwoo.
We're definitely not having
this conversation right now.
No, it's okay. It just hurt for a sec.
Come on, let's do it. Ugh.
All right, fine, what was I saying?
You were saying that I'm a...
Ahh, bad friend.
Right. You're a bad friend.
That's what I was saying to you.
- Yeah.
- And just that, you know,
you've been really blowing me
off for the last few months,
and last night you
lied to me about being sick.
- That really sucked.
- All right, well, listen.
I'm sorry I lied, Jake.
I saw you were getting upset
and I didn't want to hurt you.
But I don't know what to say
about the other stuff because
this is my life and I don't
want to apologize for that.
No, and Gina, you shouldn't have to.
Look, I'm really proud of you.
You're totally killing it.
Yeah, people want to stab me.
I mean, that's a very positive way of
- looking at things, but yeah.
- Thank you.
Ha ha ha ha-ha! Hoo hoo!
♪ I hit a new level of pain ♪
♪ Please keep talkin',
please keep talkin'! ♪
Okay, look. I just wanted you
to know that I miss you.
Well, I miss you too dude.
Great, so can we agree to
see each other like 5% more?
Deal. Aah!
We're not going to shake it.
Yeah, we'll just take
each other at our word.
Oooh! That's a knife!
That is a knife in my back.
That's so weird to say.
There's a knife in my back.
Boyle, may I speak
with you for a minute?
Sure, I was just googling
"good toys for normal children."
Nikolaj may not be a genius,
but he's a very bright child.
And on top of that, you were right.
He's also a very gifted artist.
Look what he did to my periodic table.
Sure, it's a bit
derivative of Kandinsky,
but the palette shows
an impressive comprehension
of color theory.
And he's good at clouds, too.
Okay.
I also wanted to say
I was wrong to imply
that you didn't know
what was best for him.
Oh.
You're an exceptionally
supportive parent,
and I wish my father
had been more like you.
Thank you for saying that.
And sir,
nothing would make me prouder
than being your big daddy.
Well, we're off track now.
So, uh, good day.
Hey, guys.
How you feeling, Gina?
Sometimes I feel like a nut,
sometimes I don't.
Almond Joy's got nuts.
Mounds don't.
She's very hopped up on painkillers.
Hold up, when did you learn French,
Monsieur la baguette?
Oh, as a bébé.
Oh, oui! Oui, oui, oui, oui.
It actually helps to
play along, I'm assuming.
So what's the latest?
Did you catch the perp?
No. I almost had him.
But then he jumped up, grabbed
a flagpole, spun around it
like Spider-Man, and then
flipped out of sight on a roof.
It was crazy. Officers
are still patrolling the area.
Oh, my God, that's it.
That is it! The treasure is
in the Forest of Enchanted Secrets!
- Let's go!
- No, we can't.
We have to stay here and
guard the Amulet of Destiny.
True dat, true dat.
Sarge, call me crazy,
but it almost sounds like
whoever stabbed Gina knew parkour...
just like the ex-husband of
that lady from Gina's event.
Right! Gina convinced her to leave him
and he probably wants revenge.
- I'll look into it.
- Okay.
Jake, I cannot wait for this doctor.
Will you please grab
this knife out of my back?
- Get it!
- Gina, it's already out.
What?
- Hello?
- You win.
- Please help me.
- No.
What, why? I learned my lesson.
- You were right.
- No, you were right.
For the past four hours,
I've been watching you
on the security camera.
You have? That's weird.
- This isn't about me.
- Still seems weird.
Rosa! Watching you try to open
that door and fail again
and again and again and again
was inspiring!
I was trying to teach you a lesson,
and instead, you taught me a lesson.
Great. What lesson is that?
There is nothing the human
spirit cannot overcome.
So Rosa Diaz, you are not quitting.
You are gonna open that door because
you are badass and you don't
need help from anyone!
Yeah. I'm Rosa Diaz.
You can do this, Rosa!
Uhhhhh!
She's doing it!
Uhhhhhh!
Yes!
Uhhhhh!
- You did it!
- I did it!
Oh, that was great!
I love being independent
- I have to go to the bathroom.
- Oh, okay, I'll help you.
And then you were like,
"We can use the Amulet
to fight the Queen of Tears!"
I said all of that when I was
on drugs? That's brilliant.
Yeah, we basically came up
with an entire amazing story.
- We should write a movie!
- Yes!
Jake and Gina present, colon,
"The Queen of Tears," colon,
"Battle for the Amulet of Destiny."
Colon, Part One, colon, of Five.
Oh, get those sequel profits... smart.
- Yerp.
- Oh, here comes Terry.
- Hey, sorry I'm late.
- Oh, you should be, Terrance.
You almost missed
the surprise we got for you.
- Huh, what is it?
- I think you mean,
"Who is it?"
Bryant Ungerbert?
Hello, Terry Jeffords.
It's been far too long, old friend.
We did the right thing.
- Yes we did, Gina.
- Who's Gina?
Are you still on drugs?
- Yeeeah.
- Oh, tight.
Sync & corrections by emeline-whovian
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net