So I told Nikolaj, "Who cares
if you're bad at skateboarding?
When you grow up, nobody thinks
skateboarders are cool."
What's cool is having your own pants.
- Uh-huh. Sure.
- Jake, you seem distracted.
You're agreeing with everything I say.
We should go on a month-long
couples' vacation:
- you, Amy, me, and my dad.
- Yeah, yeah, fine, whatever.
And we should get
matching hats that say,
"Best Bud 1" and "Best Bud 2."
And wear them all the time!
For sure. Look, Charles,
don't look behind you,
but I think we're being followed.
I saw this guy when we were
leaving the precinct,
and he was in line at lunch,
and now he's right behind us.
Is it someone you arrested?
I don't recognize him, but
judging by the head-to-toe denim,
I say he's either not American
or deeply American.
I'm thinking Ukraine or Kentucky.
Well, should we call it in?
No. I've got a better idea.
Hi there.
Who are you, and why
are you following me?
I'm not following you.
- I come for Charles Boyle.
- Hey, hey, hey!
- Hands where we can see them.
- Chill out, bro!
It's not gun.
It's just... uh, it's a toy.
No shoot, pretty please.
It's gift for Nikolaj.
Nikolaj? How do you know Charles's son?
My name is Gintars.
From Latvia.
I am Nikolaj birth father.
Ohh!
Nikolaj's birth father
who I'd never hope to meet.
Very cool.
Cool, cool, cool, cool, cool,
cool, cool, cool, cool,
cool, cool, cool, cool, cool,
cool, cool, c-c-c-c-c...
Sync & corrections by emeline-whovian
www.addic7ed.com
Charles, are you okay?
You hit your head pretty hard.
Oh, no, I'm fine.
I don't have a concussion.
We'll see about that.
How many musical numbers are
there in the movie "Zootopia"?
- Oh, just the one.
- Yeah, he's okay.
I don't know what's going on.
How did you find me?
The orphanage isn't supposed
to give out that information.
You know Dragomir, Nikolaj brother?
He tell me all about you.
Of course. You're Dragomir's father too.
No, Dragomir is my brother.
Dragomir and I have same father
but different mother.
Her name Anyuta.
Together we have baby.
That baby's Nikolaj.
Dragomir is brother of Nikolaj.
I am brother of Dragomir.
Also stepfather.
We are contemporary blended family.
Would make very good TV show.
Honestly, that does sound
very interesting and good.
Anyways, I was too young
and poor to have child,
but now I'm very successful businessman.
I have my own clothing line.
Maybe you've heard of it:
The Gape.
We also have Baby Gape
and the Gape Body.
- Oh, you mean The Gap?
- No, no, Gape.
Like, there are two things
and there's space between.
Yeah, like, The Gap. Like, The Gap.
The company that already exists.
I don't know what you're saying.
I never heard of it.
But is it a knock-off of Gape?
Do they sell clothing?
So what? You have money now,
and you're just gonna take Nikolaj back?
No, no, I don't want
to take boy from you.
I just want to meet him one time.
Look, I know it's lot to ask,
but, please. Nikolaj is my sex result.
Oh, yeah? Well, I walk your sex result
to school every morning.
No, don't use his words.
I help your sex result
with his homework.
This is bad, even for you.
I sing your sex result
a lullaby every night.
- I wanna do something.
- You will never meet my son.
Oh, yeah? Well, then I don't leave
America until I meet the boy.
And I come from white country.
I have very long visa.
Very long.
So I'm positive the murder
happened inside this apartment,
but CSI could find no traces of blood.
I'd like to ask the FBI to
bring in a team of lab techs.
This would require
Commissioner Kelly signing off.
Before I make that ask, is
there anything else we can do?
Um, I'm pretty sure there is.
Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
I am now.
We need Yee!
Who?
Isn't it that guy that led
that seminar where you guys
turned Boyle into a mummy,
and then you pushed him down the stairs?
- Whoa!
- Whoa! Rosa.
Easy. No one pushed
Boyle down the stairs.
Right. We may have
plastered his eyes shut
and left him to wander around blindly,
but he fell down on his own.
- It was a classic accident.
- Exactly.
Anyway, Dr. Yee is a genius
in the field of forensic entomology.
They call him "Father Fly."
- How cool is that?
- 0%.
How are insects gonna help us?
There weren't any in or around the boy.
Oh, my God.
You still think forensic
entomology is all blow flies
and screw worms, don't you?
That's a good one, Santiago.
You should take the Lieutenant's exam.
- Hey.
- Dr. Yee has recently
bred a species of fly
that has increased sensitivities
to certain human proteins.
They can detect trace amounts of blood,
even if it's been cleaned with bleach.
Or masked with animal urine.
Oh, I was building to that.
- Thanks for stealing my thunder.
- This is nasty.
Terry hates bugs.
Too many eyes and legs.
Would you still hate bugs
if I told you that
there were thousands
of tiny mites that live
in your eyebrows and keep them
from being weighed down
- by oils?
- Yes!
Look, I really think we should go
with the feds on this.
No, we're bringing in Yee.
I'll make the call right now.
- Oh, can I listen on speaker?
- Mm.
Oh, my God.
It's gonna be a long couple of days.
You're telling me.
I got bugs in my brows, Rosa.
Hey.
So what's your plan with Gintars?
He's kind of taking over
the whole waiting area.
No, don't worry about me.
I'm watching "Mad About You"
on Latvian Hulu.
It's very funny show.
Very many episodes.
I could sit here all day.
I don't know what to do.
He's never gonna leave.
But I'm scared for Nikolaj
to get to know him.
Okay, how about this?
Gintars just wants to see him, right?
We can maybe have them meet
without telling Nikolaj that
Gintars is his birth father.
Just say he's an old friend of ours.
Jake, you're completely forgetting about
the olfactory bond.
Nikolaj will immediately
recognize his father's scent.
Well, you got to do something,
and I don't think you're gonna
wait this guy out.
Paul and Jamie are
locked in the bathroom.
But Jamie has a turkey in the oven.
This is a very good setup.
- And they pay it off.
- It's so good.
Okay, Jake,
let's give your plan a shot.
Okay, Gintars, remember the deal is,
you cannot tell Nikolaj
you're his father.
Who Gintars?
I'm Billy Hanukkah.
I'm from the Bronx, Manhattan.
I eat pizza at Famous Ray's.
Okay, well, no need to get too specific
or offer up any backstory.
Hey, guys. I'm just coming from work
with my friend Billy Hanukkah.
- Hanukkah.
- It's fine.
Kids don't know which names are weird.
Nikolaj, say hi to Jake
and this stranger.
Hi, Jake. I love you.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Hanukkah.
I love you too.
Man, he really is a Boyle, isn't he?
Hello, my little friend.
Did you have good day at school?
- We had computer class today.
- I am your real father!
My name is Gintars.
- You are my son.
- What?
Well.
That backfired real quick.
Daddy, why is the man
saying he's my father?
Mr. Hanukkah is crazy.
He has no children of his own,
and it's driven him mad.
I'm your father, Nikolaj.
- It's pronounced Nikolaj.
- Nikolaj.
It's okay. You say it wrong.
Okay, well, that was fun.
Hey, why don't you go
play over there, buddy?
You can take this drug store receipt.
It's very long and filled with coupons.
You can fly it around like a kite.
Whee!
Wow, kids are really basic.
Is being a dad super easy?
What the hell was that?
You promised you wouldn't tell him.
So sorry. I smelled my boy.
I don't know what came over me.
Please. I'm in town for 10 more days.
Let Nikolaj know I exist.
Let me spend time with him.
I could take him to Russian bathhouse.
- Has he been?
- No!
I'm not some weirdo that takes
my eight-year-old
to the Russian bath!
We take our baths at home
together as a family
like normal people!
Not sure you have the upper
hand on that storm-off, Boyle.
He's here! Dr. Yee's on his way up.
How's my breath?
Perfect. Yee's gonna love it.
This is not a good color on you guys.
Speaking of bad looks,
Sarge, what is going on
with your eyebrows, man?
I shaved them off.
'Cause of the bugs.
Sharon said you couldn't notice.
Sharon lied, Terry. You look
like a straight-up fool.
Damn, Rosa.
No, Diaz is right.
Your face is horrifying.
You should leave before...
Hello, Dr. Yee!
Out back now.
Captain Holt,
nice to see you again.
Please, call me Raymond.
Unless that feels weird.
You don't have to.
I'll answer to anything.
Raymond works.
So I understand you have
a potential crime scene,
and you'd like to find some blood.
Well, I've brought along several hundred
of my best detectives to help out.
Oh, my God. I'm starstruck.
We all are.
So what you made you
think of using drosophila
as a method of searching for
blood traces?
Have you ever read Sung Tz'u's textbook
- "The Washing Away of Wrongs" from 1235?
- Nope.
- Yes.
- Which edition?
It tells the story of
the first known use
of forensic entomology.
A farmer was slashed to death.
A local judge asked everyone in the town
to lay down their sickles.
And though they all appeared clean,
one attracted a horde of flies.
The insects could sense the blood,
even though it was invisible
to the human eye.
Wow, what an arresting story.
Yes, they did arrest him.
We made a joke together.
Okay, Dr. Yee, how effective
is your box of bugs?
Oh, well, in a lab,
they've detected blood even
when it's been cleaned with bleach.
Or covered with animal urine!
You two really know your stuff.
I know that sound.
That's the moaning of a man
who left his lunch on the bus.
I didn't lose my lunch, you idiot.
I lost my son!
Okay, Scully, I got this.
Hey there, bud.
I got you your favorite tea:
- duck broth.
- Thanks.
You know me so well.
But I'm too sad to drink duck broth.
Wow, I never thought I'd hear
you or anyone say that.
Nikolaj is asking if Gintars
is really his dad.
I worked so hard to have him
think of me as his father.
And now it's all ruined.
He'll probably go back to
calling me what he did
when I first adopted him: Mr. America.
I know you're upset,
but that is a dope nickname.
I'm not Mr. America.
- I'm Daddy.
- Of course you are.
I just don't want
Nikolaj to see him again.
I don't want him turning into a Gintars.
You have nothing to worry about.
Nikolaj is already a mini Charles.
He's an eight-year-old boy
whose favorite movie
is "Bullets Over Broadway."
So what are you saying? I should
let him spend time with Gintars?
I just worry that if you prevent him
from knowing his birth father,
that he'll build up some fantasy of him
and then blame you
for keeping them apart.
That's crazy.
The way that King Trident kept Ariel
from exploring the surface.
Oh, my God, you're right.
I'm driving Nikolaj into
the arms of a sea witch.
Watching him work is amazing.
Mm-hmm.
- I have to get a video.
- Santiago, please.
Hold the phone horizontal
to get more flies in frame.
All right, guys, this fanboy
stuff is a little much.
The only thing that's
a little much over here
are your scrawled-on eyebrows.
- Yeesh.
- Seriously?
- I thought they worked.
- They do...
if you wanna look
like a mean drag queen.
I knew I should have done
a flatter arch.
This is a nighttime look.
Well, the flies are not reacting.
I can keep going, but I'll tell you now,
it's very unlikely there are
any traces of blood in here.
Well, according to my timeline,
this is the only place the
murder could have happened.
Sorry, Rosa, looks like
your timeline's wrong.
Because the flies don't lie.
You can use that if you want.
He's not gonna use a cheeky slogan.
- He's a man of science.
- I like it.
The flies don't lie.
Okay, Dr. Yee, exactly how
accurate is this technology?
Diaz, how dare you question the man.
Dr. Yee has spent millions
of dollars developing
and researching these flies.
It's fine. Would you all
like to see what happens
when they actually sense blood?
- Yeah.
- Uh-huh.
Will you hold this, Ally?
- Wow.
- I'm sorry, Detective Diaz,
I know it's upsetting when
a hunch doesn't pan out.
Well, it's over. The flies have it.
Keep your eyes on the flies.
Flies don't lie.
Now, that's a good one.
Oh, no, it's Santiago's. Damn it.
Wow, this was a bad idea.
Relax. He gets one
afternoon with Nikolaj,
and he chooses basketball?
Does Nikolaj even like basketball?
He loves the "Get Your Head
In The Game" number
from "High School Musical."
I haven't seen it, but I know
that's not the same.
Look at them. Does it seem like
he's actually enjoying this?
Porzingas!
Charles, can I tell you a story?
- Always.
- All right.
When I was 10,
my dad started dating this woman, Leeza.
My mom hated her.
But my dad wanted us to bond,
so one day he took me and Leeza
to the mall and dropped us off.
She proceeds to steal a ton
of blouses from Ann Taylor
and then immediately makes me go back in
and exchange them for store credit.
Then to celebrate,
I get to pull Leeza's Cinnabon apart
because her nails are too long
and curly to do it herself.
- Ugh.
- Point being,
nothing has ever made
me love my own mother
more than the time I spent with Leeza.
Gintars is Leeza.
You are my mom.
I can't believe I get to be Karen.
What an honor!
- Daddy, Daddy.
- Yes, sweetie?
- Can we leave?
- Oh, no, so soon?
But I understand.
We can go home right now.
No, not home. Daddy Gintars
wants to buy me a jean jacket
just like his.
Daddy Gintars.
Oh, no.
I am Leeza.
Wait. No. That's not right.
Hey, bud.
Everything going okay in here?
I know you're going through something,
but people are starting to
complain about the moaning.
Ugh. I would give anything
to have Gintars gone
and out of Nikolaj's life.
But it's not gonna happen.
Okay, well, I'm just gonna
close the door, then.
And you can feel free to moan
as much as you need.
This is bad.
I know. He's been like that all day.
No, I was talking about your eyebrows.
Whatever's going on up
there is real, real bad.
Well, it's better than having
two bug hotels above your eyes.
But wouldn't they also be
in your goatee?
- Don't do this to me, Jake.
- Wait a minute.
I may have just thought of
a way to get rid of Gintars.
Do you still have that friend
who works on the
Counterfeiting Taskforce?
Yeah, why?
Gintars has this terrible knock-off
clothing brand called The Gape.
If I can get him to admit on tape
that he's selling counterfeit goods,
they would terminate
his visa and deport him.
Deport him?
Doesn't that seem a little extreme?
Yeah, definitely, but Charles just said
he'd give anything
for Gintars to be gone.
- He's not doing great, Terry.
- Okay.
But how are you gonna
get Gintars on tape?
Good question, Sergeant Crazy Brows.
Gintars is always talking
about the Russian baths.
I'll see if he'll meet me there
and then ask him to cut
me in on his business.
Meanwhile, I'll have a mic
hidden underneath my towel.
It's foolproof.
Before we do deal, we take off towel.
It's full naked.
Ha.
What are you waiting for?
I want to see where your
hair starts and stops.
Gintars.
Take it off now.
Heh.
Hey, Sarge.
Holy crap. What the hell is that?
That is a bug-free zone is what it is.
I bleached it.
I'm smarter than they are, Rosa.
Uh-huh. What about your nose hair?
Oh, man. Terry forgot about his nose.
Hey, why is Yee still here?
Holt wants him to hand in
his case report in person.
I think he's trying to trick him
into going to lunch with him.
Wait. It's noon?
If I didn't know better,
I'd say that was lunchtime.
I hope they take that
container of bugs with them
- when they go.
- Wait. The container's here?
I have an idea.
All I need is some blood.
This is fresh.
Oh. Terrible, yet perfect.
Stupid bugs didn't do anything.
He lied to us, Sarge.
Huh?
Why's your towel still on?
This is business conversation.
You cannot trust a man who
cannot show you his full self.
Well, not in America.
Here we have business
meetings fully clothed.
Sometimes even in a suit and tie.
Have you ever seen the show
"Shark Tank"?
Latvian "Shark Tank" is all nude.
That sounds weirdly sexy.
No, not at all.
There's no female sharks,
so it's just four Mr. Wonderfuls naked
on a big leather couch.
Huh. Not what I imagined.
Hey, listen.
I would love to buy some
of that knock-off denim.
Okay, first of all, it's not knock-off.
Okay, Gape is true, authentic brand.
The real thief is Gap.
- Are they?
- What makes more sense?
That they take Gape and remove letter?
Or that I take Gap and add pricey E?
I don't care if it's fake,
I just wanna buy some.
It's not fake;
you are still wearing a towel;
and this deal: over.
Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
Do you wanna know why
I won't take off my towel?
It's because I'm embarrassed...
about what's underneath.
Mutilated penis?
Ye... p.
That is it. You guessed it
on the first try.
That's what's under there.
The old... the old...
mute peen.
I am so sorry about your penis.
It's a bummer.
But we all have things
that bring us shame.
Remember when I told you before
that Gape was original, authentic brand?
I do. It was just now.
Yeah, well...
I stole the whole thing from Gap.
And here I was completely believing you
when you told me you didn't.
Wow.
Well, thank you for
sharing that with me.
You are freak.
But I support you. Come.
Oh, no, it's a naked hug.
Ha ha. Ah.
Hey, what's up? You guys having
a little coffee? That's cool.
- Yee's a fraud.
- What?
Excuse me?
Those nasty-ass bugs don't smell blood.
And they must not
smell bullcrap, either,
'cause he's spewing it everywhere.
What are you saying out
of your weird face?
We put the flies near fresh blood,
and nothing happened.
They didn't react at all.
Do you know how stupid
these accusations sound?
- Diaz, you're fired.
- What?
Dr. Yee is one of the most respected
forensic experts in the country.
For you two... let's not mince words...
common fools to suggest
that you found the flaw
- in this brilliant man's...
- They're right.
- What?
- Huh?
The flies don't sense blood.
They're just regular flies.
But, Dr. Yee, you can't be a fraud.
You gave a TED Talk.
I spent $6 million in federal
grant money on this experiment
and I've gotten nowhere.
The closest I ever came
was when they all landed
on a Popsicle once.
But in the apartment we saw
them react to a cotton swab
- dipped in blood.
- It was melted Popsicle.
Jam works, too, but it's more expensive.
So, Sir, you were saying
something about us being
common fools?
So who looks stupid now?
Uh, Terry, your left eyebrow is missing.
Oh, I must have rubbed it off.
There it is.
Who looks stupid now?
Jake, hey, I got it, man.
Nice jeans, and the good thing is
look... both legs, same length.
Thank you very much.
And I see it's 100% denim-ish.
"Caution: Do not wear near
women who are pregnant
- or breast-feeding."
- This is true.
The nipple may fall off.
Hey, guys.
Gintars said to meet him here.
I didn't realize you were coming.
My man, I'ma wrestle you. Come here.
Charles, what are you doing here?
Why is Nikolaj here?
Oh, he's been so happy
since he met Gintars.
I've been focusing on myself
and not really thinking about Nikolaj.
- Mm-hmm.
- I didn't realize how much
it meant to him to know
he hadn't been abandoned.
I'm okay with them having
a relationship.
Wow, that is so great of you, Charles,
but I really wish you'd included me
in your decision-making process.
- Why?
- No reason.
I just maybe went in a different,
less-mature direction.
Hey, maybe we should leave
this area, like, right now.
Cop car. How's it going?
Hey, man.
Gintars Irbe, you're under arrest
for selling counterfeit goods.
Jake! You set me up.
Do you even have mutilated penis?
No.
It's perfect.
Okay.
So they're taking Gintars to the airport
and they're not hurting him...
any more than they did when
he was resisting arrest.
Now they won't let him go
just because I asked them to
even though they arrested him
just because I asked them to.
It's a crazy system.
I don't understand it.
But here's what I'm thinking:
- I call the State Department...
- You've done enough, Jake.
That's nice of you to say, but...
- My tone wasn't nice.
- But your tone is always nice with me.
Wait a minute. Are you mad?
Yes, because you butted into a
situation you shouldn't have.
You need to keep your butt
in your pants.
My butt was only out because you said
you wanted Gintars gone.
Well, thanks to your butt,
Nikolaj feels like he's been abandoned
all over again.
Okay, but my butt was
the one that got them together
in the first place.
I don't feel like my butt
is getting credit for that.
Well, that's because your butt
was inappropriate then too.
Your butt should have never
been a part of this.
So now I gotta go clean
up the big nasty mess
that your butt made.
But my butt no but...
My butt no but!
Diaz, Jeffords,
Santiago would like to apologize
to you for her behavior.
I thought we were both apologizing.
No, I misunderstood.
What would I be apologizing for?
- The same thing as me?
- Really?
You guys maybe want to have
this conversation on your own?
Yes.
- _
- Okay, we have come to a decision
that we would both like to apologize.
We should have trusted
your instincts over Dr. Yee
and his flies.
And?
And we shouldn't have been so insulting.
I'm not gonna apologize for your face.
That mess is clearly on you.
- Fair enough.
- I'll ask Commissioner Kelly
to approve your initial request
for an FBI lab team.
That won't be necessary.
I solved the case.
And the flies actually came in handy.
These have been genetically engineered
to detect blood, and
there's a whole swarm of them
at your apartment right now
with Dr. Ronald Yee.
The flies don't lie.
- He confessed immediately.
- How about that.
Dr. Yee and his flies
saved the day after all.
No, I did.
Should we call Yee and
tell him the good news?
It would probably make
him feel so much better.
- What is going on?
- He did seem so sad.
- So sad.
- He should be sad. He's a fraud.
Shh. It's ringing.
Hey.
Did you make it to the airport
in time to see Gintars?
Yes, but TSA wouldn't let him
stay in the country.
At least Nikolaj got
to spend a few hours
with his birth father at a Chili's Too.
Chili's As Well.
Listen, I feel bad, and I
wanted to do something
but I know you didn't want my help,
so long story short,
I made us these hats.
I obviously love them.
They don't change how I'm feeling.
Okay.
Well, I'm sorry that I messed things up.
But I was just trying
to be a good friend.
I know, but that doesn't
always mean fixing my life.
You shouldn't have done
anything without asking me.
Sometimes I just want you to listen.
Right.
I hear that.
It's just... adoption is complicated.
No matter how much I want to be,
I'm not Nikolaj's real father.
Come on, Charles. Of course you are.
Well, that'll be up to him.
And he may even change his mind
about it throughout his life.
I mean, all I can do
is make him feel safe
and give him as much love as I can.
Well, I think Nikolaj is
very lucky to have you.
Nikolaj.
Okay. Let's take these hats
out for a spin.
I've waited long enough.
Here you go. Best Bud #1.
You'd rather be Best Bud #2?
I just want you to listen a little more.
I don't wanna change our whole dynamic.
Okay, good, 'cause I really
wanted to be Best Bud #1.
- I know you did.
- Clink!
- Oh, they're way too small.
- Ooh, they're tight.
- They're way too small.
- Hurt.
They don't fit.
Sync & corrections by emeline-whovian
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net