.
[microwave beeping]
- So you guys are gonna tie up
the only microwave
for 20 minutes
to make a frozen lasagna?
Ballsy.
- You ignorant loser.
First of all, it's not
just a frozen lasagna,
it's a Mama Magglione's.
- Second of all, it's gonna
take 21 1/2 minutes.
The box says 20, but we know
better than the box.
- You see, this microwave
is a KitchenPro Max.
- Bit of a lightweight.
- It's only 1.2 kilowatts.
- Fine for popcorn.
- But we're talking about
a Mama Magglione's here.
- Takes a lot
to get mama hot.
- She's a real
size-queen.
- Well, that started out fun,
and here we are at our normal
ending place: disgusting.
- Uh-oh.
Guys!
We have
a major problem here.
No garlic bread.
- Okay, we need to stay calm.
Let's think.
The garlic bread needs
to go in the toaster oven
with eight minutes
left on the lasagna.
Maybe we could run down
to the corner store
and make it in time.
- That just gives
us 12 minutes
to go to a place
and come back.
- Mama Magglione.
- We have to go now!
- Okay, well,
good luck with that,
weirdos.
- Stupid piece of crap.
- Rosa, come on.
You can't
break a mouse in half.
[mouse crunches]
- Oh, wow, you did.
Scary. You really
earn your rep.
- Stupid internet.
The network's been down
all morning,
and my girlfriend--
- Jocelyn.
- Right.
She's leaving town
for two weeks.
- Oh, is Jocelyn leaving town?
Where is Jocelyn going?
- Dude, you forgot
her name one time.
It's not a big deal.
You don't have to keep
proving you remember it.
- [laughs]
That's not
what's happening here.
I'm just saying it a lot,
because she's
so important to me.
- Okay, what's her last name?
- Uh-oh.
- Mm-hmm. It's Pryce.
- Right.
- She's leaving town
for two weeks.
I want to send flowers
to her hotel room.
- Aww, that's sweet.
I wish Amy would
send me flowers.
- Why is it taking Holt
and this I.T. guy
so long to fix
the internet?
One Police Plaza sent him
an hour ago.
- Huh.
Why does Holt look so worried?
- What are you talking about?
He looks exactly
like he always does.
- To you, perhaps,
but I finally learned
how to read his emotions.
His lips are slightly pursed,
and he's blinking at
eight-second intervals
as opposed to his normal 10.
[gasps]
Oh, my God.
He's having a meltdown.
- "Meltdown" seems excessive.
- Yeah, it's a meltdown.
Mark my words.
Hey, there, Captain.
Everything okay?
- No, I'm having
a meltdown.
- Props. That was amazing.
- Thanks. It was a lot of work.
- This is Sergeant Knox.
- From Cyber Operations.
- He's discovered the reason
for our network issues.
A hacker is attempting
to break into our servers.
- Not all of them.
Just the LACMI server.
- Well, that's good.
- No, Captain Holt's nostril
just twitched. It's bad.
- It's devastating.
- Props again.
- Thanks, again.
- The LACMI server holds
clearance-protected
information, including the
names of our undercover agents.
If it's compromised, people
could lose their lives.
- Okay, but isn't
the server secure?
- Yes, but the hacker's
already used an ARP
to resolve the host name
with the DNS server.
- Uh-huh. ARP. DNS. Totally
following what you're saying.
- Right now, they're trying
to get root access
by connecting the OSI network
to the data-link.
- You know, I'm a bit
of a computer nerd myself,
but could you, maybe dumb it
down a bit for my friends here?
- They're almost
through our defenses.
If we can't stop them, they'll
be inside of our server in...
19 minutes.
- Mama Magglione.
[upbeat music]
- A countdown clock, green text
on a black background:
we are in full-on
action-movie mode.
Now all I need is my
no-nonsense captain to tell me
to focus,
because time is running out.
- Peralta.
- Yes?
- You have something
in your teeth.
It's, uh,
quite off-putting.
- What? No.
"Time is running out."
I fed you your line.
No one ever has something
in their teeth in a movie.
Watch a movie,
stupid Holt.
- Damn it, I tried to remove
the server from the chain,
but the hacker
blocked the protocol.
- Why don't you
just unplug it?
That's what I do any time
I'm having computer trouble.
And also I code a lot.
Java, mainframe.
This guy knows
what I'm talking about.
- The NYPD servers have
internal backup batteries.
Even if we unplug them, they'll
stay on for another two hours.
- As a captain, I have an
override code I can use
to wipe the servers clean
so there'd be no information
for the hackers to steal,
but there's one problem, Jake.
- Yes, sir?
- You still have something
in your teeth.
You tried to get rid of it,
but it's made it
much more prominent.
- Why would you stop everything
just to tell me that?
- It's very distracting.
Anyway, I can't use
my override code,
because doing so would delete
the entire evidence
tracking database.
The NYPD only backs up
that information
at the precinct level
twice a year.
We would lose four months
of evidence.
- So what you're saying
is that every perp
awaiting trial
would walk free?
- Exactly, and we have
hundreds of open cases.
Wiping the servers
is not an option.
The only solution
is to track down the hacker.
- How? It could be anywhere
in the world--
Osaka, Berlin,
Macau, Stockholm.
Are you guys just gonna
keep letting me list cities
I've lived in?
- Wait, the LACMI server
isn't wired to the internet.
It's supposed to be offline.
How are they accessing it?
- They must be going
through a physical AP.
- Again, these guys don't get
computers like you and I, so--
- It's not
a remote connection.
The hacker's inside
the building.
- Let's mobilize.
Nobody in or out of the
building without authorization.
Check every inch
of every floor.
And, Jake.
- Oh, let me guess.
It's on another tooth now.
Is it somehow on my face?
- No, what I was
going to say is, we only have
15 minutes left.
You need to focus,
because time
is running out.
- Oh, yeah.
That's what the F
I'm talking about.
Thank you, sir.
[indistinct chatter]
- What's all this?
- Drunken brawl broke out
between to sororities.
We're keeping
the Lambda Nus up here,
and the Kappa Gamma Kappas
are in holding on two.
They're all so mean.
- They're kids, Boyle.
I'm sure they're
just scared.
- Yeah, we're just scared kids.
Can we please go home now?
- I'm sorry, we have
to process you, but I promise
we'll go as fast
as we can.
- I hope you get shot
in the line of duty.
- Oh, my God.
- All right.
Brush it off, Sarge,
we've got an emergency.
There's a hacker
in the building.
- Look for anyone you don't
recognize using a computer,
or plugged in to a port.
- I initiated
lockdown protocol.
I'll search the fourth floor.
Peralta, Diaz,
start on one, work your way up.
Jeffords,
take Boyle, start on three,
work your way down.
- On it.
- I'll grab the keys
to the first floor.
- Smart.
[cell phone ringing]
Ames, I love you,
but I can't talk right now.
- I just got an alert that
the Nine-Nine is on lockdown.
I'm on my way.
- Wait, aren't you
at the dentist?
- Yeah, I left. It's fine.
It's a new hygienist,
and to be honest,
her scraping technique
was a joke.
- We have 14 minutes
to find a hacker.
You're not gonna
get back in time.
- But everybody else
is there, right?
I mean, it seems weird
to have this big thing
happen without me.
- We talked about this, Amy.
You have an unhealthy fear
of missing out on work.
You have FOMOW.
- This isn't FOMOW.
It's not like
I'm freaking out or anything.
Out of my way, you old bitch!
This cab is mine.
I'll be there in 10 minutes.
I love you.
Don't solve it without me.
- I got the keys.
Let's go.
Jocelyn.
- Jocelyn Pryce, hey.
- What are you doing here?
Shouldn't you be
at the airport?
- Yeah, uh, I wanted to stop
and see you on the way there.
I think we need to talk.
- Why? Is something wrong?
- I should've done this last
night, but I chickened out.
We need to break up.
- Ugh.
Mama Magglione.
.
- You want to break up?
But I just met
your college friends.
Are you telling me I had
to talk to Matt for nothing?
- Rosa.
- I thought you liked Matt.
- Matt is a nightmare.
He kept saying
"hashtag tell me
about it."
- We should really get going.
- Listen, I just
don't understand
why this is happening.
- Look, I love being with you,
but how often
am I actually with you?
- We're together every night.
- Unless you're at work,
or doing work,
or thinking about work.
It's like you never
have time for me.
- I'm sorry, but Rosa
doesn't have time for you.
We have a really
important work thing.
That was bad.
Let me try rephrasing it.
You are not as important
as Rosa's job.
Oh, wow.
That was way worse.
- Look, we just have to take
care of this one thing.
It's an emergency.
Then I'll be right back
and we can talk about this.
- I really have
to get to the airport.
- Please.
- Okay, fine.
But I'm leaving
in 10 minutes.
- Okay, just wait
in the break room.
Don't sit on the couch.
It's full of farts.
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm great.
I love being dumped.
It's super great.
- I think you're
being sarcastic,
but it's hard to tell with your
voice the way it always is.
- We just checked the third
floor. We didn't find anyone.
- We're on our way to one.
- You didn't even start yet?
- Rosa took a long
time getting ready.
You know how ladies
be preppin'.
Ow! I was just
covering up the truth
so it wouldn't
be awkward.
- Ooh, did something
awkward happen?
I can probably relate.
Dish, bish.
- Rosa got dumped
out of the blue
because she cares so much
about her job and doesn't spend
enough time with Jocelyn.
Ow! There's no winning
with you.
- Oh, so you got dumped,
and you didn't see it coming.
Oh, brother,
you are in Boyle Country.
Here's what you're
gonna want to do.
- Come on, Boyle.
- Beg her to take you back,
and don't be afraid to cry.
I'm talking tears and snot.
- Quinn, did you
get the alert?
- Yeah, but I haven't seen
anyone unusual down here.
I mean, other than 1,000
Kappa Gamma Kappas.
- At least you didn't
have to deal with Lambda Nus.
Those girls are savages.
- Right? We're
the victims here.
We have a nighttime event, and
if we don't make our blowouts,
then we'll all
look disgusting,
and nobody will give
any money to the kids,
or dogs, or whatever
the charity is.
- It's to buy shoes for poor
people so they can get jobs.
- Yeah.
- We'll do our best,
but it's possible
you're gonna miss your event.
- That's too bad, 'cause you
could use some decent shoes.
- What? Terry got
these at Aldo.
- Was it buy one, get one?
- No, it wasn't.
It was a three-for-one
Labor Day doorbuster.
- Makes sense.
- Come on.
[cell phone rings]
- Nobody on the fourth floor.
- Three is clear.
We're finishing up two.
I gotta get out of here
before the sorority girls
notice my tie.
- Just regroup
in my office.
[line trilling]
- Go for Hitch.
- Hitchcock, damn it.
I meant to call Peralta.
We're in the middle
of a crisis.
- Oh, no. Is it the lasagna?
- The what?
- Don't play dumb
with me, Raymond.
What's wrong
with the lasagna?
- I have no idea what
you're talking about.
- What is it? What's wrong
with the lasagna?
Is it bubbling over?
- He won't tell me.
- Captain, give us
the damned information.
Is it bubbling over?
- I don't have time
for these shenanigans.
- What's the problem?
- He wouldn't say.
- Oh, no.
Then it must be bad.
Call Jake.
He'll tell us the truth.
[line trills]
- Hitchcock?
- Give it to us straight, man.
- What's going on?
- Uh, just searching
the first floor.
- Searching the first floor?
- Why is the lasagna
on the first floor?
- What? Are you talking about?
The lasagna is fine.
- Oh, thank God.
He says it's fine.
Oh, you're a saint, Jakey.
I love you.
- Okay. Holt's texting me.
Love you, too.
Rosa!
We gotta go up to Holt's.
- Is this not done yet?
Ugh.
Jocelyn leaves
in eight minutes,
and I don't want things
to end like this.
- Wow.
Way to be vulnerable.
I thought for sure
you'd write her off
the second she said
she wanted to break up.
- Yeah, I did.
She's dead to me.
- Wait? Then why
are you so anxious
to get back up and
talk to her?
- Because I have a plan.
I'm gonna beg her to stay,
change whatever it is
I need to change,
then once our relationship
is stronger than ever,
I'm gonna dump her ass
so quick.
It's gonna be brutal.
- Okay, I'm gonna try
and put this nicely.
That is psychotic.
Okay, maybe not psychotic,
but it's like something
the lady
from "Killing Eve" would do.
Not Sandra Oh, Villanelle.
You know, the crazy one
who stabs everyone
with her hairpin.
But--have you still
not watched "Killing Eve"?
I've told you about it
so many times.
- Look, I've never
lost a breakup,
and I'm not starting now.
I'm 12-0.
I'm always the dumper,
never the dumpee.
- I just don't think
every breakup
has a winner and a loser.
- Sounds like somebody
who's lost all his breakups.
- [scoffs]
Not all.
Maybe like half, max.
Just--being generous.
[phone rings]
- Hey, Ames.
- Cab was too slow.
Decided to walk.
It's nice to take
a little stroll.
You're clearly running
at full speed.
- Whatever.
How's it going there?
- Not great.
We still haven't found
the hacker.
- Oh, super.
I mean--oh, no.
- Is Amy FOMOWing?
- Of course not.
- Big time.
Okay, I gotta go, babe.
We're headed to Holt.
- Don't you dare
hang up on me!
I am part of this.
- Rosa, this is dumb.
I'm just gonna go.
- No, no, no.
You promised me more time.
I still have
seven minutes.
- I really don't
want to miss my flight,
and I cannot
physically stand
the way that room
smells anymore.
- Just breathe
through your mouth.
Please, just stay here.
I'll be right back.
- We searched everywhere.
No hacker.
- Maybe he camouflaged himself.
Maybe he's a real-life
Peeta Mellark, out there
looking like a river rock.
- I hate to say it,
but maybe it's time
we start thinking
about erasing the server.
- No, not until
the last possible minute.
What else can you do?
- I've been trying
to pinpoint him.
I've been making my way
through the server sockets,
trying to determine which port
he's plugged into.
- What's going on?
I can't hear anything.
Turn me around.
I'm missing everything.
Part of the team.
What's up, team?
- Is Sergeant Santiago
suffering from FOMOW?
- No.
- [mouths words]
[distant commotion]
- What's happening?
- I think the hacker just
opened the holding cell.
[women chattering indistinctly]
- Mama Magglione.
.
- Oh, no.
They're running free.
- Everyone, cover up
your worst physical attributes.
- It's no use.
They could always
find new ones.
- Why would the hacker
open the holding cell?
- Maybe he's trying
to create a distraction.
I think he can see that I'm
closing in on his location.
- Then keep doing that.
The rest of you,
get them back
into holding.
- Oh, come on.
Get down from there.
- Do you know who my father is?
He's in business.
That's where you actually
make money at your job.
- I make money.
I make good money.
- That can't be true.
Otherwise, you wouldn't
still have that chin.
- What? Nobody ever said
anything about my chin?
Boyle, is something wrong
with Terry's chin?
- I don't want to get involved.
- Oh, my God. It's true.
- How is she running so fast
in those shoes?
- She's too drunk
to feel any pain.
- Open up.
- No.
- You are trapped in a very
small room, and we can see you.
What's your plan here?
- Shut up, I'm trying to think.
If you come in here,
I'll bite you with this
weird mouth thing.
- That is a staple remover,
and it's shocking
you don't know that.
- Sorry, I'm not
a secretary.
- I don't have time
for this.
My girlfriend leaves
in three minutes.
You are ruining
my life.
- You're ruining
I missed my
Drybar appointment
without calling
to cancel first.
They keep record
of those things.
- Oh, my God, neither of your
lives are being ruined.
I told you I'm not on board
with your psycho plan
to destroy
your girlfriend.
- I'm not gonna destroy her.
I actually want her back.
- I really love her, Jake.
- What? Rosa, then why'd you
say all that stuff
about winning
the breakup?
- Because it's weak and
humiliating to love someone.
I lied to make myself
feel strong and normal.
- Right, that's definitely
what came across,
how normal
you were being.
[door opens]
- Don't let her go.
You guys, I used to have
this boyfriend, Jason,
then we broke up 'cause
I got drunk at Spring Fling
and passed out in a bush, and
he took too long to find me,
and now he's gone
and it's like,
there's no one to find me
when I pass out in a bush.
- I'm not sure
that totally applies here.
- No, she's right.
I can't let Jocelyn go.
Can you handle this
without me?
- Yeah, it's under control.
Go get Jocelyn back.
- Jocelyn Pryce.
- Do you need to use a phone
to make a call?
- Gross, I don't know
any phone numbers.
- Where the hell
did Jocelyn go?
- Elevator.
Tears and snot.
- [grunts]
- [scoffs]
Where are you going?
I still have one minute left.
- I'm leaving because
it's clearer to me than ever
that your job is more important
to you than I am.
- That's not true!
- Sorry, ma'am, I can't
let anyone in or out.
- She's with me.
- You don't even apologize
blow me off.
You just text
"Double homicide TTYL".
- Sometimes I add
those little heart emojis.
You know how uncomfortable
that is for me.
I'm sorry.
My job is hard.
- Yeah, it is, and it's
important, and you help people,
but I need more.
- I promise I'll try.
- Honestly, I just don't
see it changing.
- Move, move, move!
Oh, no,
why are you outside?
Is it over?
Did we catch the hacker?
- No, I have a personal thing
that's more important to me.
- Oh, yeah, work-life balance.
I have that, too.
- Sorry, I can't--
- Andrew, it's me!
Come on, come on, come on.
- Got it.
- What?
- Time check.
- Five minutes, ten seconds.
- It's over.
- Don't say that.
- We'll never get the garlic
bread toasted in time.
- We can, and we will.
- How?
- We'll set the oven to 500.
- Are you insane?
It'll burn.
- We'll wrap it
in foil.
- The foil will stick
to the cheese.
- That's a risk
we'll have to take.
- Move it.
- Hey, you made it.
- Yeah.
- We finally got all the
Lambda Nus back into holding.
- Who are
the Lambda Nus?
Doesn't matter.
I'll read your notes later.
- I didn't take any notes.
- What the hell, Jake?
Do you even love me?
- Says the woman who
never once sent me flowers.
Never mind, uh, we still
haven't found the hacker,
but the cyber guy
is getting close.
- Okay, let's check
in with Holt.
- Hold on to him, girl.
He seems pretty sweet, and you
guys are like both sevens.
- Oh, come on.
- We only have
two minutes left.
I'm telling you,
I can't find him.
- Captain, maybe it's time
to face reality.
We have to erase
the servers.
- I'll initiate
the sequence for you.
It just needs
your passcode.
- Perhaps you're right.
How depressing.
I never would've thought that
typing an intricate sequence
of numbers from memory
would bring such sadness.
- Hi, I'm Sergeant Santiago.
I'm sure these guys have
told you all about me already.
Long story short, nothing
happens around here without me.
[computer chimes]
- What is that?
- We just got an NOS ping
from the first floor.
The hacker is in room 103.
- [gasps]
Mama Magglione.
.
- Go, go!
Room 103!
- What are we gonna do?
It's still frozen
in the middle!
- Well, then turn up the temp.
- It's already at 500.
It's maxed out.
- Then set the mother[bleep]
to broil!
- Okay!
Geez.
- I thought you said
you searched
the entire
first floor.
- I did. I even checked
the ceiling for clingers.
- Hey, who's that guy
from Cyber?
- Sergeant Knox. We've been
talking computers all day.
Pretty technical stuff.
I kept up.
- His face is really familiar.
I can't place him.
- It's empty.
- And there's nothing plugged
in to the internet port.
- But Knox said
he got a NOS ping.
I mean, NOSes don't just
ping themselves, guys.
- Jake, stop.
You're not fooling anybody.
You don't anything
about computers.
- [scoffs]
Oh, my God.
You're right.
I'm not fooling anybody.
- I was fooled, Jakey.
You're my computer boy.
- No, no, no.
I don't know anything
about computers.
None of us do.
And Knox could tell that.
So he knew that
we wouldn't catch on
if he just
made stuff up.
What if the reason
we can't find the hacker
is because
there is no hacker?
- Why would Knox lie
about that?
- What if he doesn't
actually care
what's on the LACMI servers?
Maybe his real goal
is to just trick Holt
into erasing
all the servers.
He might just be trying
to delete some evidence.
- So you think
he's a criminal.
- Oh, my God.
We have to go right now.
I know how
I know Knox.
He's the guy
from the security footage
in the Avery Street murder.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, he shaved his beard,
but it's definitely him.
- We have less than a minute.
- Call Holt.
- Knox is right next to him.
He'll hear everything.
Here, I'll text him.
- I don't get it.
Holt was about to erase
the servers.
If that's what
Knox wanted,
why did he
stop him
and say the hacker
was in room 103?
- I don't know.
Maybe to get rid of us.
No, to get rid of you.
The second you showed up
in Holt's office,
he sent us away
and the holding cell doors,
they opened when I walked in
with Amy on my phone.
He must've known
that she would recognize him.
Why is this taking
so long to send?
[cell phone chimes]
- What's going on?
We're running
out of time here.
- Uh, sorry, it's uh--
from my husband, Kevin.
- Well, all due respect, but
you don't have time for that.
You've got 15 seconds
before the hacker
is inside the server.
- Uh, yes, uh--it's just that
Kevin just texted me some
hot goss about our favorite
reality TV star.
- 10 seconds.
Your agents' lives
are at stake.
Eight, seven--
- Oh, I understand.
I just have to find out
about the hot goss.
- "How certain are you?
Sincerely, Raymond Holt."
"100 percent, sincerely"--
Why am I doing that part?
Send.
Okay, it said delivered.
Make way, make way.
- Peralta, Santiago,
you'll be happy to know
that I did not
erase the server.
- Oh, thank God.
- But sad to know
that Knox caught on
and is now
holding me at gunpoint.
- Why not lead with that?
- Nobody has to get hurt.
Just put your guns down,
and put your hands in the air.
- Hey! I said
put your guns down,
and get your hands
in the air.
- The bread,
it's gonna burn.
- Guys, do what he says.
I'll buy you all
the garlic bread you want.
- We're gonna hold you
to that, Sarge.
- Knox, you're pointing a gun
at an NYPD captain.
Have you really thought
this through?
- This is not my fault.
You were supposed to be
at the dentist.
- What?
How did you...
You called me.
He called me.
He said he had a tip
for the officer in charge
of the Avery murder.
I said I could meet any time
except for this morning
because of the dentist.
- I had it
all planned out.
- Guess you didn't count
on my FOMOW.
Yeah, that's right.
It's crippling.
- Oh, picking a weird time,
but I'm glad
you're finally owning it.
- Here's what's
gonna happen.
The captain and I are gonna
walk out of here real slow.
No one's gonna
move a muscle.
Everyone's gonna be okay.
Now we're just gonna move.
[microwave beeping,
siren blaring]
- He's down. He's down.
We got him.
- Jeffords, get him
into holding.
- With pleasure.
You're about to have
a really bad day.
Give me that.
Look at his pants, ladies.
They're relaxed fit.
Uh-oh.
Is that a braided belt?
- Whoa, what happened?
You know what, forget it.
I'll just read Amy's notes.
- Why aren't you guys
on your way to the airport?
- Oh, I'm gonna miss my flight,
but it's worth it.
It means a lot that Rosa bailed
on all this just for me.
- Aww.
- You did what, Diaz?
- Now, sir, I told her
it was okay.
If you're gonna be mad
at anyone, be mad at me.
- Okay, I am mad
at you.
- What?
No.
I didn't think you
were really gonna be mad.
That's--that backfired.
Be mad at Rosa.
- Worst morning ever.
- Yeah, it was stressful,
but we got the guy.
Surprised you two
are taking it so hard.
- We were talking
about our lunch,
you self-absorbed
son-of-a-bitch.
- Come on.
- Look at this bread.
It's completely inedible.
There's not even
any soft parts
in the middle
we can pull out.
- Title of your sex tape?
- We cooked that lasagna
for nothing.
Nothing!
- Okay.
But have you
ever considered
eating lasagna
with no garlic bread?
- We've...
Never done that before.
- I guess maybe
we could give it a try.
What do you think,
Hitchcock?
- What the hell.
I had a feeling
something crazy
was gonna happen today.
- There you go.
- It's almost ready.
[microwave dings]
- Mama Magglione.
- Mmm.
Mmm.
- Not a doctor.
Shh!
- Fremulon.
www.tvsubtitles.net